thewwwblog.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy : The WWW Blog

The privacy of our visitors is important to us.

Third Party Advertising  
We use Google, Kontera, Amazon, Share A Sale, Advertising.com, Tribal Fusion, SixApart and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this web site in order to provide advertisements on this site about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the links provided below.

Google – http://www.google.com/privacy.html  
Sixapart – http://www.sixapart.com/privacy/  
Kontera – http://www.kontera.com/privacy.aspx  
Amazon – Amazon.com Privacy Notice  
Share A Sale – http://www.shareasale.com/w3c/policy.html  
Advertising – http://advertising.aol.com/privacy  
Tribal Fusion – http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html

Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers, including those listed above, may place or recognize a unique “cookie” or web beacon on your browser

What are cookies?  
A cookie is a file that tracks a user or customer’s preferences on pages visited while on a website. On our website we may use cookies or third parties may do so on our behalf.

Should you accept a cookie, each subsequent visit to our site will identify you and collect and compile anonymous statistics related to your interests, tastes, purchasing intentions and general uses of the sites.

The data collected by the cookie is compiled and used in the future to market other products and services or advertisements to you, to analyze the usage of our website to provide data on how to improve the website and for feedback generally. No sensitive personal data or personally identifiable data capable of identifying you as a private individual are collected.

All data are for specific purposes for our private use only and not for use of any other third party unless specifically instructed by us and only for a specific purposes, such as marketing of products and services.

Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

Your Choices  
You do not have to accept cookies and you may block or disable all cookies from your browser at anytime.

Most web browsers will accept cookies by default, but they can be set to reject cookies, either from all websites or from specific sites. You can also manually delete cookies from your web browser. These options are generally set through a “Privacy” setting in your browser setup.  
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. You may also opt-out of receiving cookies from third party advertising networks by using the [NAI Opt-out Tool](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
